#### Contact

apowell4@ecommunity.com

www.linkedin.com/in/angie-powell-msn-rn-cmsrn-7a1452a9 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Healthcare

Hospitals

Nursing

#### Certifications

Certified Medical-Surgical Registered Nurse - CMSRN

# Angie Powell MSN, RN, CMSRN

Director Of Inpatient Nursing at Community Howard Regional Health Kokomo, Indiana Area

# Summary

Experienced Nurse Leader with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Acute Care, Medical-Surgical Inpatient Care, Team Engagement and Change Management. Strong operations professional with a Master's degree focused in Nursing Leadership and Management.

## Experience

Community Health Network Director of Inpatient Nursing August 2018 - Present (2 years)

Indiana University Health 10 years 4 months

Manager of Clinical Operations August 2016 - August 2018 (2 years 1 month) Indianapolis, Indiana

RN Shift Coordinator September 2010 - August 2016 (6 years) Indianapolis, Indiana

Registered Nurse May 2008 - September 2011 (3 years 5 months) Indianapolis, Indiana

### Education

Western Governors University

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Healthcare

Management · (2020 - 2022)

# Western Governors University Master's degree, Nursing Leadership and Management · (2014 - 2016)

Indiana University Kokomo
Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing · (2004 - 2008)